{
  "pollList": [
    {
      "0": {
        "index": 0,
        "question": "How would you rate your experience?",
        "answer": "UnLike"
      },
      "1": {
        "index": 1,
        "question": "How would you like about our service?",
        "answer": "Happy"
      },
      "2": {
        "index": 2,
        "question": "How would you like about our quality?",
        "answer": "Satisfied"
      },
      "id": "714a"
    },
    {
      "0": {
        "index": 0,
        "question": "How would you rate your experience?",
        "answer": "UnLike"
      },
      "1": {
        "index": 1,
        "question": "How would you like about our service?",
        "answer": "Like"
      },
      "2": {
        "index": 2,
        "question": "How would you like about our quality?",
        "answer": "Happy"
      },
      "id": "c594"
    },
    {
      "0": {
        "index": 0,
        "question": "How would you rate your experience?",
        "answer": "UnLike"
      },
      "1": {
        "index": 1,
        "question": "How would you like about our service?",
        "answer": "Like"
      },
      "2": {
        "index": 2,
        "question": "How would you like about our quality?",
        "answer": "Happy"
      },
      "id": "af74"
    },
    {
      "0": {
        "index": 0,
        "question": "How would you rate your experience?",
        "answer": "UnLike"
      },
      "1": {
        "index": 1,
        "question": "How would you like about our service?",
        "answer": "Like"
      },
      "2": {
        "index": 2,
        "question": "How would you like about our quality?",
        "answer": "Happy"
      },
      "id": "a552"
    },
    {
      "0": {
        "index": 0,
        "question": "How would you rate your experience?",
        "answer": "UnLike"
      },
      "1": {
        "index": 1,
        "question": "How would you like about our service?",
        "answer": "Like"
      },
      "2": {
        "index": 2,
        "question": "How would you like about our quality?",
        "answer": "Happy"
      },
      "id": "4471"
    },
    {
      "0": {
        "index": 0,
        "question": "How would you rate your experience?",
        "answer": "UnLike"
      },
      "1": {
        "index": 1,
        "question": "How would you like about our service?",
        "answer": "UnLike"
      },
      "2": {
        "index": 2,
        "question": "How would you like about our quality?",
        "answer": "Like"
      },
      "id": "1bea"
    },
    {
      "0": {
        "index": 0,
        "question": "How would you rate your experience?",
        "answer": "UnLike"
      },
      "1": {
        "index": 1,
        "question": "How would you like about our service?",
        "answer": "Like"
      },
      "2": {
        "index": 2,
        "question": "How would you like about our quality?",
        "answer": "Happy"
      },
      "id": "917c"
    },
    {
      "0": {
        "index": 0,
        "question": "How would you rate your experience?",
        "answer": "UnLike"
      },
      "1": {
        "index": 1,
        "question": "How would you like about our service?",
        "answer": "Like"
      },
      "2": {
        "index": 2,
        "question": "How would you like about our quality?",
        "answer": "Happy"
      },
      "id": "c1c7"
    }
  ]
}